Cover Letter And Skills

My name is William Nordqvist and I am 31 years old. I am born and raised in Stockholm. I graduated from KYH this summer (2020) where I have been studying to Front End Developer for the last 2 years.

I have a background working with Community Operations Management for tech Companys and have for the last 10 years working for Apple, iZettle and Uber. I really loved to work with fast-growing company's and I have learned a lot from that, but I felt that I wanted to work more with my creativity and work more independently. That Is why I started to study to Front End Developer.

I have chosen to work as much as possible with React combined with SCSS or Styled Components during my time in school since I want it to be my expertise. I am now searching for new job opportunities. My dream employer is where I can continue to develop my skills in React. But I am also open to learning new libraries and languages such as Svelte, Angular or Vue. My long term goal is also to work as a full-stack developer and would also love the opportunity to work with more Backend languages.

What is important to me?

My desire is to work with a company that I feel passionate about, that shares my ambitions and my drive to grow the business. I want to work for a company that I feel proud of and that challenges me to be engaged daily.

I would love the chance to further discuss the position and what skills I would bring to the job. Thank you for considering my application.

Kind regards. William Nordqvist +46723121941 wnordqvist@gmail.com http://www.wnordqvist.com/

Framework Libraries/API Language • HTML (2 years) • React (2 years) • Styled Component (2 years) • CSS (2 years) • Svelte (1 year) • Semantic UI (2 years) • JavaScript (2 years) • Node.js (1 year) • Express.js (1 year) Platform Tools Storage

- Visual Studio Code
- xcode

MacOS

- Firebase
- MySQL
- MongoDB

Work Experience	
Insurley App - Internship FrontEnd Developer	2019 - 2020
Work tasks: • Maintaining and Develop features and functionality	
Stureplansgruppen Web Developer Work tasks: • Building their new website – https://www.stureplansgruppen.se/ • In charge of Maintaining och updating all sites connected to Stureplansgruppen	2019 - 2020
Uber Community Operations Manager Work tasks: Manager for the Nordic Support team. Launching Uber Support team in Casablanca and Lithuania. Alignment of policies across Nordics countries. Interviewing and hiring for advanced support team. Develop and improving new support futures/function. Such as Phone and Chat support.	2015 - 2018
Teleperformance - iZettle Junior ACM/ Project Manager Work tasks: • Launching iZettle outsourcing Nordic team • Recruiting and interviewing new CSR to the team • Planning monthly and annual budget and project KPIs • Monthly personal and KPI follow-up meetings for each CSR • Coordinating Global KPI	2014 - 2015
Teleperformance - Apple CSR Work tasks: • 5 Months IOS - Premium Customer service for iPhone Users • 5 Months CPU - Premium Customer service for Mac Users	2013 - 2014
Customer Nordic Customer service	2008 -2011

Work tasks:

 \bullet Coordinates hotel weekend and events to our customers, CRM system.

Education	
KYH Stockholm - Front End Developer	2018 - 2020
Front End Developer http://kyh.se/project/front-end-developer/	
Sälj och Marknadshögskolan	2011 - 2013
International sales and marketing http://www.smhsverige.se/	
KFS Gymnasium	2005 - 2008
Business and Administration	

Mälarhöjdens skola

References

Alok Alström - General Manger Uber Sweden.

William comes to work with a positive attitude and is not afraid to help out. Even in some cases where colleagues have dropped the ball on their ticket duty William is constructive and positive when re-engaging them for support. He has also shown leadership strength in setting up a structure and calendar for tickets in Sweden as well as training the support specialists in Lithuania.

He makes sure that the tickets gets done in time, sometimes and the expense of his own work life balance. He has also been a valuable asset to reduce the ticket burden to the Sweden team while at the same time helping to set up the support center in Lithuania.

Lina Areblad - Marketing Manager Uber Sweden

Patience – I've heard William talk to our most upset riders on the phone. I have not met many people in my life with his patience. He listens and does everything he can to make sure our riders are happy.

William has great energy and positive attitude at work and around the office. He's a team player and great colleague that adds to a great team spirit. This is surely one reason why he's good at handling Support problems and rider concerns accordingly. Never afraid to take a tough call!

